&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：从观察的角度定义闭包，而不是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To define closure from an observational perspective, rather than
从一个是否存在的角度来看，学术问题。
from a whether it exists or not sort of a perspective, the academic question.
这是这个定义，就我而言，
Here's that definition, and as far as I'm concerned,
从现在开始这就是面试问题的正确答案，
this is the right answer to that interview question from here forward,
直到有人告诉我一个不同的答案，一个不同的定义
until somebody tells me a different answer, a different definition that
比这个更精炼，我还没见过。
is more distilled than this, which I haven't come across.
这就是这个问题的正确答案，什么是闭合？
This is the right answer to that question, what is closure?
闭包是指函数能够记住和
Closure is when a function is able to remember and
访问它的词法作用域，它外部的变量，
access its lexical scope, the variables outside of itself,
所谓自由变量，当它能够访问词法作用域时，
so-called free variables, when it's able to access that lexical scope,
即使当该函数在不同的作用域中执行时也是如此。
even when that function executes in a different scope.
让我们来看第一部分。
Let's take that first part.
该闭包能够访问其词法范围。
That closure is able to access its lexical scope.
我们已经知道了。
We already know that.
这就是词法范围本身，就是函数可以引用外部变量
That is lexical scope in itself, is that a function can reference variables outside
它只是沿着作用域链向上找到它。
of itself and it just goes up the scope chain to find it.
第二部分是关键部分，没有这两部分，
The second part is the critical part, and without these two parts,
你没有了结。
you don't have closure.
你必须两者兼得。
You have to have both.
没有第二部分，它只是一个词汇范围。
Without the second part, it's just lexical scope.
这个定义的第二部分，也就是，即使函数
With the second part of this definition, which is, even when the function
在不同的作用域中执行，现在我们开始看到一些有趣的东西。
is executed in a different scope, now we start to see something interesting.
因为当您接受一个函数并将其作为回调传递时，或者
Cuz when you take a function and you pass it as a callback, or
您获取一个函数并将其返回，以及它最初的作用域
you take a function and return it back, and the scope that it was originally
否则，至少在概念上，已经消失了。
defined in has otherwise, at least conceptually, gone away.
我们会想，通常情况下，它已经被垃圾收集了，已经完成了。
And we would think, normally, it's been garbage collected, it's done.
但在这个范围内定义了一个幸存的函数。
But there's a function that survived that was defined within that scope.
事实证明，这个范围根本没有消失。
It turns out that the scope didn't go away at all.
事实证明，这个函数能够保持对该作用域的引用，并且
It turns out that this function is able to hold on to a reference to that scope, and
无论您在哪里传递函数，它都可以继续访问该函数。
wherever you pass the function, it continues to have access to that.
这不是偶然发生的。
That doesn't happen by accident.
那不是魔法，那是结束。
That's not magical, that's closure.
保存，链接回定义它的原始范围，
The preservation, the linkage back to the original scope where it was defined,
无论您将该值传递到何处，
no matter where you pass that value,
无论它在哪里执行，它都会保留该值。
no matter where it executes, it retains that value.
它保留了这个范围。
It preserves that scope.
这就是所谓的结束。
That's called closure.
所以让我们来看几个例子，
So let's take a look at a couple of examples,
那些你可能马上就会认出的东西。
ones that you'll probably recognize right off the bat.
当然，你们所有人都在某个时刻做过计时器，设置了超时或
Surely, all of you have done a timer at some point or another, a set timeout or
一个设定的时间间隔，我打赌当你把一个函数传递给你的计时器时，
a set interval, and I bet when you passed in a function to your timer,
它引用了自身外部的一些变量。
it referenced some variable outside of itself.
同样可能的是，你从来没有停下来考虑，这是如何工作的？
What's also probably true is you never stopped to consider, how does that work?
因为在这个函数waitASec运行时，
Because at the time that this function waitASec runs,
Ask函数已经完成，并且
the ask function has already finished, and
它关闭的变量问题应该已经消失了。
the variable question which its closed over should have gone away.
但它并没有消失，因为闭合保存了它，
But it didn't go away because closure preserved it,
所谓的waitASec函数在变量问题上是封闭的。
so-called the waitASec function is closed over the variable question.
这是个了结，好吗？
That's a closure, okay?
现在，在学术上，他们在每个变量的基础上考虑闭包，
Now, academically, they think about closure on a per variable basis,
意思是只有我关闭的变量，
meaning only the variables that I'm closed over,
这些是唯一保存下来的。
those are the only ones that are preserved.
从技术上讲，有可能是这样的。
Technically, it's possible that that could be the case.
当然，这只是你所能观察到的。
Certainly, that would only be what you could observe.
但我想提醒你的是，一般说来，
But I would caution you to consider that generally speaking,
至少我所掌握的最新信息，JavaScript引擎基本上
at least the latest information that I have, JavaScript engines essentially
将闭包作为到整个作用域的链接来实现，而不是在每个变量的基础上实现。
implement closure as a linkage to the entire scope, not on a per variable basis.
从技术上讲，它们应该能够关闭单个变量或
Technically, they should be able to close over individual variables or
删除未关闭的变量，但是
remove variables that aren't closed over, but
基本上，就我所知，关闭是基于每个作用域的。
essentially, as far as I'm aware, closure is on a per scope basis.
所以，如果你有一个变量，它持有一个非常大的数据片段，并且
So if you have a variable that's holding on to a really big piece of data and
然后创建一个闭包，即使你没有引用它，
then you create a closure, even if you're not referencing it,
这些数据可能会留在附近，而不会被垃圾收集。
that data may stick around and not get garbage collected.
所以最好假设闭包，即使在学术上它是每个变量，
So it's best to assume that closure, even though academically it's per variable,
最好假设闭包是基于作用域的操作。
it's best to assume closure is a scope-based operation.
这不是你必须对一个函数做特别的事情，
And it's not something you have to do special with a function,
除了你只需要在外部访问一个变量
other than you just have to access a variable outside and
然后你必须在某个地方传递函数。
then you have to pass the function somewhere.
这就是您所要做的所有事情，以观察闭合存在的想法。
That's all you have to do to observe the idea that closure exists.
想象一下如果你有一个没有闭包的函数会是什么样子。
Think about what it would be like if you had a function that didn't have closure.
如果您所在的语言具有一流的函数、词法范围，但是
If you're in a language that had first class functions, lexical scope, but
没有闭包，你应该在某个地方传递这个函数，然后
didn't have closure, you'd pass this function somewhere, and
突然之间，它会忘记所有的变量。
all over sudden, it would forget about all its variables.
不会有多大帮助，不是吗？
Wouldn't be that helpful, would it?
这几乎就像是关闭作为一种必要的要求，一种必要的
It's almost as if closure falls out as a necessary requirement, a necessary
具有第一类函数的词法范围语言的第三个组件。
third component of a lexically scoped language with first class functions.
如果你有这两个，
If you have those two,
你会有个了结因为不这样做是没有意义的。
you're gonna have closure because it wouldn't make sense not to.
这就是结束。
That's what closure is.
不管你做不做定时器，你肯定都写过或者
And whether you do timers or not, you've certainly all written or
至少访问了返回函数或
at least accessed code that returns functions or
在回调中传递它们，这是完全相同的事情。
passes them around in callbacks, and that's the exact same thing.
如果我在这里返回一个在问题变量上关闭的函数，
If I returned a function here that is closed over the question variable,
那么即使Ask函数已经完成，通过行11，
then even though the ask function has finished, by line 11,
我们仍然可以访问该变量。
we still have access to that variable.
不是变量的快照，而是实际变量本身。
Not a snapshot of the variable, but the actual variable itself.
这就是所谓的结束。
That's called closure.